<resources>
    <string name="app_name">solar</string>

    <string name="desc">
        01. <b>Renewable energy source:</b> Solar panels generate electricity from sunlight, which is a renewable and abundant source of energy.\n\n
        02.<b> Cost-effective:</b> Once installed, solar panels can provide energy at a lower cost compared to traditional sources of energy, such as fossil fuels.\n\n
        03. <b>Reduced carbon footprint:</b> Solar energy is clean and does not produce harmful greenhouse gas emissions, which helps to reduce carbon footprint and combat climate change.\n\n
        04. <b>Energy independence:</b> Solar panels can provide energy independence by allowing individuals and businesses to generate their own power, reducing dependence on the grid.\n\n
        05. <b>Low maintenance:</b> Solar panels have few moving parts and require minimal maintenance, making them a low-maintenance source of energy.\n\n
        06. <b>Increased property value:</b> Installing solar panels can increase the value of a property, making it a worthwhile investment for homeowners and businesses alike.\n\n
        07. <b>Versatility:</b> Solar panels can be installed in various locations and sizes, making them a versatile energy solution for a range of applications.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="feedback">Your Feedback</string>

    <string name="feedbk">
        Your Feedback
    </string>

    <string name="feedbackView">
        01. love this app! It\'s so user-friendly and makes my life so much easier.\n\n
        02. This app is amazing! It has everything I need to stay organized and productive.\n\n
        03.  I\'ve been using this app for a while now and it\'s been a game-changer. It\'s so easy to navigate and the features are fantastic.\n\n
        04. I\'m so glad I found this app. It\'s helped me stay on top of my tasks and be more efficient.\n\n
        05. This app is perfect for what I need. It\'s simple and intuitive to use, and I\'ve had no issues with it so far.\n\n
        06. This app is amazing! It has everything I need to stay organized and productive.\n\n
        07. I\'m so glad I found this app. It\'s helped me stay on top of my tasks and be more efficient.\n\n
        08.  I\'ve been using this app for a while now and it\'s been a game-changer. It\'s so easy to navigate and the features are fantastic.\n\n
        09. This app is perfect for what I need. It\'s simple and intuitive to use, and I\'ve had no issues with it so far.\n\n
    </string>


</resources>